The 12th fret of the guitar
is the end of the cycle of scales.
Up
is the rebirth of eight notes.
While stop
represents the last sound.
I think
life is the same.
Sometimes,
the point isn't choosing
right or wrong,
but having someone who
can hear the resonance with you
when you're most scared.
This is for you.
This is...
I think
it suits you.
Thank you.
I'll keep it.
[Smile After Tears]
[The 12th fret: Resonance of choices]
After losing He,
I felt lost.
I thought I found my direction.
But
[Senior He]
I was just going in circles.
I really want to finish He's song.
When you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears.
I'll smile and say goodbye from afar.
My brother smiled a lot
during that time.
[When you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears.]
He must've shared a lot of
[When you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears.]
his happiness with you.
But no matter how bright the sky gets,
it will finally get dark.
The most important thing is
that you're still here,
and you can start again.
Junjia.
Where are you?
[High School Hot Music]
It's over.
What should we do? It'll be our turn soon.
I'll text him now.
He's not the kind of person
who doesn't answer calls.
Is it Junjia?
You should get ready.
Okay, right away.
What should I do?
[The Star of Life Ambulance Co., Ltd.]
[No vehicles allowed]
Sir, are you okay?
Diaoqin.
Great.
You're fine.
I'm fine.
A car rushed over.
I dodged.
But
someone got hurt,
so I stayed to help.
But
my phone was broken.
That's good.
Let's go.
Everyone is waiting for you.
Did he pick up?
Call that junior.
Junior?
I'm here.
[High School Hot Music]
Junjia, you're finally here.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Good.
Tie,
let’s get ready outside.
Okay.
Junjia, don't be nervous.
Leave your things here.
We'll wait for you outside.
Hurry up.
We'll wait for you.
I'll take your chain out for you.
I’ll talk to the organizer.
Junjia.
I'll wait for you outside.
Jiayi.
He.
I've used many chances
to open the door many times.
I finally get to see you.
You know what?
I've been looking for you for a long time.
But every time,
you didn't turn around to look at me.
I had six chances
to say goodbye to you.
Junjia.
It’s okay.
We've been practicing a lot lately.
It's just a small injury.
Look.
If it hurts,
why didn't you tell me?
That's it for today.
I’m leaving.
Junjia.
I'm always by your side.
Jiayi.
I miss you so much.
I miss you too.
I'm sorry
I can't be with you anymore.
He.
Promise me.
Even without me,
you have to believe that
you deserve to be loved.
Can't you stay a little longer?
I...
Do you remember
we made a wish
at the aquarium?
At that time,
I wanted both of us to be happy.
Happiness
doesn't mean we have to be together,
but to live well.
We will be heartbroken since we can't
get our love,
and sad because we lose each other.
But we still need to take
our love seriously.
At least,
we really loved each other.
That's enough.
This is happiness.
Just remember me.
When you stand on the stage
and sing the words "turn around",
imagine I'm by your side.
When you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears.
[BACKSPACE]
I'll smile and say goodbye from afar.
♪ Watching you drown in sadness ♪
♪ In your tears ♪
♪ I wonder what love is ♪
♪ It's when you're alone,
someone is by your side ♪
♪ It's when you're lost,
someone points out the right direction ♪
♪ Though you have nothing,
you won't turn around ♪
♪ But you are in midsummer ♪
♪ In spring flowers ♪
♪ In the aurora full of sky ♪
♪ I can only wait for you ♪
♪ I can't be afraid of you getting hurt ♪
♪ It reminds us that
freedom is also a cage ♪
♪ Between us ♪
♪ Repeating ♪
♪ After you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears ♪
Jiayi,
♪ Hugging and hovering, only in dreams ♪
you finally sing
♪ After you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears ♪
your voice.
♪ Hugging and spinning,
in the room that doesn't exist♪
Time's up.
♪ Hope, hope again ♪
♪ You have no tears ♪
♪ I'll smile from afar, goodbye ♪
[BACKSPACE]
Thank you
for letting me know how love feels.
[BACKSPACE]
[Live]
Today's guests are very special.
[Studio 1]
They are
BACKSPACE, the high school band
that gained much popularity
in the competition with an original song.
Welcome to our show today.
Say hello to everyone, okay?
Hello, we're BACKSPACE.
First of all,
on behalf of our audience,
I'd like to ask you a question.
What's your creative idea
about this song?
This song is
for those who lost something.
Okay.
Let's listen to this song first.
♪ Watching you drown in sadness ♪
♪ In your tears ♪
♪ I wonder what love is ♪
♪ It's when you're alone,
someone is by your side ♪
♪ It's when you're lost,
someone points out the right direction ♪
Regret
is like a shadow.
♪ Though you have nothing,
you won't turn around ♪
Wherever you go, it will be here.
♪ But you are in midsummer ♪
♪ In spring flowers ♪
♪ In the aurora full of sky ♪
But
it reminds us
♪ I can only wait for you ♪
the sun used to shine on us.
♪ I can't be afraid of you getting hurt ♪
♪ It reminds us that
freedom is also a cage ♪
♪ Between us ♪
♪ Repeating ♪
♪ After you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears ♪
♪ Hugging and hovering, only in dreams ♪
♪ After you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears ♪
Regret is not because we lost something,
♪ Hugging and spinning,
in the room that doesn't exist♪
♪ Hope, hope again ♪
but because
we once possessed it.
♪ You have no tears ♪
This is a part of life.
♪ I'll smile from afar, goodbye ♪
[Live]
Without regret,
life will be boring.
Thanks to regret,
we cherish
every minute
and every second.
I hope what we lost in the end
can become the most beautiful memory.
[Junjia]
Hello.
Junjia.
[Dalang, Korean Skewers,
Fried Chicken, Drinks]
One for each.
Thank you.
You did a great job.
Take these
as a token of our gratitude.
Please enjoy your meal.
-Thank you, sir.
-Thank you.
It doesn't matter that
you didn't win a prize.
You're popular and even on the radio.
I love to be a popular guy.
As the president,
I have to say one thing.
Although we don't have
a ranking this time,
we're the most popular band.
It's more worth it than the trophy.
Yes.
What's important is we did it together.
This song will stay in our hearts forever.
It doesn't matter whether
we get anything or not.
The most important and happiest thing is
we can finish the song together.
Let's...
Wait.
We two also want to toast with you.
Yes, we want to toast with you.
[Dalang, Korean Skewers,
Fried Chicken, Drinks]
-Come on.
-Cheers.
Losing is scary.
Regret will break your heart.
But
once you go through it with someone,
you'll understand
tears
are never the end,
but to let us remember
the traces of love.
If you
go to America,
remember to bring me a souvenir.
I'll think about it.
No.
You must bring me a souvenir.
Okay.
[My Guitar Friend]
[Closed]
Even though it's closed,
music is still there.
And these instruments
are still shining.
Life is the same.
No matter what happens in the end,
we have to keep
shining.
It's time
for me to leave.
Okay.
Can you wait for me?
I'll be back soon.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Even though I have to leave,
I don't feel lonely,
because when I turn around,
someone will always
be waiting for me to say,
"Goodbye."
The saying "Goodbye"
is another way to say
"We'll meet again".